// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [{
        numb: 1,
        question: "Which of the following is not a valid JavaScript variable name?",
        answer: "5myValue",
        options: [
            "myValueS",
            "none of these",
            "5myValue",
            "myValue"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 2,
        question: "What happens when a function executes a return statement?",
        answer: "A value is returned and the function execution stops",
        options: [
            "A value is returned and the function execution stops",
            "An error message is generated",
            "A value is returned and the function execution continues",
            "none of these"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 3,
        question: "_____ allow you to group a series of statements together to perform a specific task.",
        answer: "Functions",
        options: [
            "coercion",
            "Objects",
            "Functions",
            "variables"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 4,
        question: "variables in JavaScript can be declared with what keyword?",
        answer: "var",
        options: [
            "for",
            "document.getElementByld ",
            "var",
            "obj"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 5,
        question: "Sometimes a function needs specific information to perform its task. In such cases, when you declare the function you give it _____",
        answer: "Parameters",
        options: [
            "Parentheses",
            "Arguments",
            "Parameters",
            "Variables"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 6,
        question: "Which attribute is used with the <td> tag to merge two cells?",
        answer: "rowspan-2",
        options: [
            "merge-row2",
            "rowspan-2",
            "colspan-2",
            "merge-colspan2"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 7,
        question: "Complete the following sentence by choosing the correct answer: In HTML,____________",
        answer: "not all tags have to have a closing tag",
        options: [
            "all tags must have a corresponding closing tag",
            "not all tags have to have a closing tag",
            "no tags have closing tags",
            "there are no tags"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 8,
        question: "Which of the following is the correct rule to prevent users seeing content that is bigger than the box containing it?",
        answer: "overflow: hidden;",
        options: [
            "overflow: hidden;",
            "overflow: scroll;",
            "display: none;",
            "overflow: visible;"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 9,
        question: "Which attribute is used with image tag (<img>) to display text if the image cannot load in the browser?",
        answer: "alt",
        options: [
            "id",
            "description",
            "alt",
            "link"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 10,
        question: "Which organisation defines world wide web standards?",
        answer: "World Wide Web Consortium",
        options: [
            "Microsoft Corporation",
            "Google",
            "TCP/IP",
            "World Wide Web Consortium"
        ]
    }
    // uncomment  below code and make duplicates to add more questions
    // but remember you need to give the numb value serialize like 1,2,3,5,6,7,8,9.....

    //   {
    //   numb: 11,
    //   question: "Your Question is Here",
    //   answer: "Correct answer of the question is here",
    //   options: [
    //     "Option 1",
    //     "option 2",
    //     "option 3",
    //     "option 4"
    //   ]
    // },
];